# Tacoyia Jones

(469) 230-9962 Lashayyjones@gmail.com

# **Professional Summary**

A diverse Medical Office professional experienced in Administration, Receptionist, Billing and Coding, ordering and administrating supplies, and General Office. The ability to demonstrate, establishing customer rapport, and provide exceptional service to both coworkers and customers. Offer computer skills in Microsoft Office, Excel, PowerPoint and Outlook.

# Key Skills & Highlights

- Typing 40 wpm
- CPR certification
- Insurance Verification
- Billing
- Entering customer information
- Scheduling
- Inventory
- MS Office

#### Education

Concorde Career College, Grand Prairie, TX Medical Office Administrator Program 2017 - Present

## Externship:

67 Pain and Injury

#### **Medical Office Administrator**

- Greeted incoming patients
- Answered incoming phone lines
- Took patient insurance information
- Assisted new patients with paperwork
- Scheduled patient appointments
- Vitals
- Setup and assisted patients with their therapy exercises
- Watched, observed and documented patient therapy to ensure they are completing all exercises
- Maintained neat and clean exam rooms between patient visits
- Restocked exam rooms
- Audited files

## Experience

Convergys 1/2017 - 04/2017

### Customer service specialist

- Inbound calls from patients with questions about their At&t digital life security systems
- Billing and payments ... adjustments, discounts etc.
- Troubleshooting
- Account adjustments
- Scheduling technicians
- Processing orders (Upgrading or Downgrading Equipment)
- Checking security systems are working properly

# Tacoyia Jones

(469) 230-9962 Lashavyjones@gmail.com

Rite Care Pharmacy 12/2015 - 04/2016

### Customer service Representative

- Outbound calls to patients regarding their medications
- Obtain insurance information
- Refill customer medications
- Process payments, changed customer personal information
- Inform customer on their coverage for medication offering lower pricing for medications
- Informing customer if their prior authorizations where approved or denied
- Organizing all work through spreadsheets

#### Teleperformance

# Customer service Representative

10/2015 - 12/2015

- Inbound call regarding customers Humana insurance
- Verified customer benefits
- Billing and payment
- Prescription Pricing
- Finding doctors in customer service area
- Updating customer demographics information

Walmart 3/2015 – 7/2015

#### Sales Associate

- Greet customers and provide excellent customer service
- Water plants inside/ outside
- Cashier
- Bagging items
- Cash, check and credit card handling
- Stock products on shelves
- Scan extra merchandise and stock in the back room

#### **Digital Badges:**



Click here to see more badges

10/2013 - 12/2013